Why did you have to do that for me?
你这小子干吗袒护我？
Mind your own business, you bastard.
不要多管闲事好吗？混账
I don't want to owe any more favors.
我已经受够欠别人人情了
If we get out, we'll be even.
如果我们逃得出去 就算互不相欠了
Thank goodness…
太好了
I knew you are still alive, Chainsaw.
你果然还活着 电锯
Die!
去死吧
It hurts so bad!
痛死我啦
Heal!
痊愈
It won't work, Chainsaw.
没用的 电锯
It hurts so much!
好痛
My heart is not here.
我的心脏不在这里
You can't kill me.
你是杀不死我的
Devil…
恶魔
Doesn't look good.
大事不妙
Denji keeps losing blood.
淀治不停失血
His chainsaw will retract if that continues.
再持续下去 那个电锯会缩回去的
-How pathetic. -Chainsaw.
真可悲
The chainsaw retracted. I'm out of blood.
电锯缩回去了 血量不够
You lost.
是你输了
-Die. -Chainsaw.
去死吧
Even blood as revolting as sewer water
就算是臭水沟般的难喝脏血
would taste like strawberry jam
只要一边欣赏你痛苦的表情一边喝
when I see the agony on your face.
就跟吃草莓果酱一样爽
The Devil Hunters that the Devils fear…
恶魔会害怕的恶魔猎人
are the ones who are nutcases.
是脑子有问题的家伙
Sahara was too sane.
佐原那个人个性正经
That's why he died.
所以他死了
And Subaru.
昴也很正经
And Sasaki.
佐佐木也很正经
A sane person would fear the Devil's attacks.
由于为人正经 不禁会害怕恶魔的攻击
And the fear makes the Devil stronger.
而恐惧会变成恶魔的力量
He's a sane one too?
他很正经吗？
No sane person would try to kill that Gun bastard.
想杀死枪混蛋的人没一个正经的吧
You joined Public Safety to kill Gun too, didn't you?
你不也是为了杀枪混蛋 才加入公安吗？
No, I'm not.
并没有
Exactly.
是啊
You are no exception.
你不是例外
Most Devil Hunters dream of killing Gun.
大部分的恶魔猎人都想杀死枪混蛋
All honest and simple people.
坦率、正直又单纯
So the Devils know how to make them afraid.
所以恶魔知道如何激起你们的恐惧
But there's no way of knowing what a nutcase is thinking about.
然而脑子坏掉的家伙在想什么 无从得知
Devils fear what they can't understand too.
即便是恶魔 仍会害怕无法理解的事物
Master, you drink too much.
师父 你喝太多酒了
Stop. That's what a sane one would say.
停 这句话也太正经了
It takes years of work to loosen up a few screws.
需要日积月累 使头脑的螺丝松脱
Visiting your partners' graves every month.
每个月定期来帮搭档扫墓
That only keeps them on tight.
螺丝会一直拧得很紧喔
I'll head back now.
我先回去了
Aki's still a rookie. Train him up.
秋还只是个新兵蛋子 你要好好锻炼他
I'll take my time.
我会循序渐进的
You can't.
不能慢慢来
That kid's collecting pieces in earnest.
秋那小子是认真在收集肉片
It won't be long before he finds Gun.
再过不久就能找到枪混蛋了吧
No.
我不要
Aki.
阿秋
Wanna hop to the civilian side with me?
要不要跟我一起跳槽到民间企业？
We won't have to find Gun anymore.
去了就不必寻找枪混蛋
We can grab lunch at places like this.
午餐可以来这里或其他餐厅吃
And watch a movie after work once in a while.
下班回家偶尔去看个电影
That's not a bad way of living.
每天过这种生活也不错嘛
I can drink with you whenever you want.
你想喝酒的话 我随时奉陪
But I'll never be a civilian Hunter.
但我绝对不会去民间工作
I'm taking that almond tofu.
杏仁豆腐我拿走了
Give me a cigarette then.
那给我一根烟吧
If Aki fights the Gun Devil, he'll get killed for sure.
万一跟枪之恶魔交战
It's not because we aren't strong enough,
并非因为我们目前实力不足
or because that Devil can kill hundreds in a blink.
也不是因为对手是 能一眨眼杀死数百人的恶魔
It's because Aki is cool,
因为阿秋很帅气
serious, gentle…
认真又温柔…
and normal, like everyone else.
跟大家一样 都是普通人
But…
但是…
It hurts…
好痛
I…
成…
I did it…
成功了
If it's this guy…
如果是这个男人…
I just had a genius idea.
我想到一个点子
You get cut and bleed.
你被我砍伤流血
I drink your blood and recover.
我就喝你的血复原
Then there's a perpetual motion machine!
永动机就完成啦
The Nobel Prize is mine!
这下子诺贝尔奖就是我的了
If it's this absolute nutjob,
如果是这个脑子坏得最彻底的男人
he might actually be able to kill Gun.
搞不好有办法杀死枪混蛋
The pain…
好痛
Aki, are you still alive?
阿秋 你还活着吗？
How long…
多久…
How long has it been?
大概过了多久…
Three days or so… after that.
在那之后…过了三天左右吧？
Meowy…
喵子…
Let's go have a drink.
大家一起去喝酒吧
It's over. I want to sleep a bit.
事情结束了 我想先睡一下
It's over?
结束了吗？
This is my weakness.
这里就是我的要害
-This is my heart. -Kill me.
-是我的心脏 -快点杀了我
-I'm sorry. -I apologize.
-对不起 -非常抱歉
-I can't take any more pain. -It hurts.
-承受不了更多痛苦了 -好痛
Already?
这么快就结束啦？
But it feels so good, like taking a dip in the pool.
这样就像泡在泳池里
We're out.
成功出来了
We got Gun Devil's piece.
还拿到了枪之恶魔的肉片
And the weather is so good.
而且天气超好
It feels like I just took a nice dump.
跟拉完屎一样爽快
It feels like I'm floating…
好像轻飘飘的…
He fell asleep…
他睡着了…
He fought that Devil for days without any sleep.
因为他不眠不休地宰杀恶魔
We'll take Aki and Denji to the hospital.
我们会带阿秋跟淀治去医院
You two report back to the Sector.
你们两人去报告这次的经过吧
A newbie welcome party?
迎新会？
Yes.
对
Division 4 has never gotten together before.
因为四课从未全员集合过
Let's bond as a team and solve our latest problem.
让我们加深感情
Problem?
问题？
Thing is, Kobeni and Arai want to quit.
问题就是 小红跟荒井说不当公安了
It's not just a fear of the Devils.
他们不止是害怕恶魔
They probably regret now that they tried to kill Denji.
也很后悔动了想杀死淀治的念头吧
You wanted him dead too, Himeno.
姬野前辈你还不是一样想杀了他？
Yeah.
对啊
I can't believe kids nowadays will quit over such petty things.
现在的年轻人 竟然因为这种小事就不干了
We should live shamelessly.
还是厚脸皮地活下去吧
If it's at the drinking table,
去喝酒的话
we could apologize to Denji
就能爽快地跟淀治道歉
and persuade Kobeni and Arai to stay.
还能挽留小红他们
You just want to drink, don't you?
你只是想喝酒吧？
It's small, but I found a piece.
虽然很小 但找到肉片了
If we're going drinking, it has to be this week.
要喝的话一定要约在这星期
I want to invite Ms. Makima.
既然要喝酒 那我想找真纪真小姐一起
She's going to Kyoto on a work trip next week.
真纪真小姐下周要去京都出差
I heard that she's going there to request assistance
听说是因为淀治被恶魔盯上了
since Denji got targeted by a Devil.
她为此去请求支援
So we should do it this week.
所以我想挑这星期喝酒
Seriously,
说真的
what do you think Denji is?
你觉得淀治是何方神圣？
That Devil seemed to know something about him.
我们对付的那个恶魔 似乎知道淀治的事
And I've never seen anything like that form before.
而且我还是第一次见到那种形态
The biggest question is why Ms. Makima cares so much about him?
最令人不解的是 真纪真小姐居然很关心淀治
Ms. Makima…
真纪真小姐…
Normally, she travels all the time. But she's been staying in Tokyo lately.
经常东奔西跑 最近却待在东京
That's because of Denji, right?
就是因为淀治在这儿吧？
Could be because she knows his secret.
说不定是因为她知道淀治的秘密
Should we get her drunk and make her talk?
要不要灌醉她 问个清楚？
-Cheers!
干杯
The food smells so nice.
这些闻起来好香
-Nice. -So much food.
-超痛快 -可以吃上一辈子吧
-There's so many. -Take it.
拿去吧
Which first?
要先吃哪个？
Nice beer.
真好喝
-I haven't drunk for half a year. -It smells amazing.
-我半年没喝酒了 -超香的
Same here. Other than a little at home.
我也是 顶多在家小酌
Get away. The sashimi is all mine.
闪开 生鱼片通通归老子
What's this? Looks tasty.
这是什么？看起来超好吃
Sorry, I got lost.
不好意思 我刚才迷路了
Kobeni, come sit here.
小红 来这边坐
Ms. Makima said she'll be late.
真纪真小姐说她会晚到
Three parfaits, and…
给我们三份圣代 还要…
The Shiratama dumpling tray. Three of those.
白玉团子套餐 三份好了
I've never had anything so delicious.
我第一次吃这么美味的饭菜
You send most of your salary home, right?
小红的钱几乎都要寄回家里吧？
Eat up, okay?
要多吃点喔
Hands off! Thief!
小偷 不准抢走
The fried chicken is all mine!
炸鸡全都是老子的
Fushi, you didn't bring your Fiend?
伏先生不带你那边的魔人来吗？
I didn't dare.
我不敢带过来
Hey! You're young! So order more!
喂 你还年轻 再点几道菜 吃饱一点
The hell? I can't read most of this.
搞什么啊 没几个看得懂的汉字
KISU TEMPURA
（沙鮻天妇罗 ※沙鮻音同接吻）
Hey, about my kiss…
我问你 说好的接吻…
I'm too shy to do it sober.
没喝醉我会害羞
Wait till I get drunker.
等我喝醉一点再亲
I'll give you an intense one.
我会给你一个浓厚的深吻
Forgive us for trying to kill you, okay?
原谅我们之前想杀了你 好不好？
Totally. Sure thing.
超级原谅 超原谅
Your name, age, and the Devil you have a contract with.
报上姓名、年龄和你签约的恶魔
You should only tell people you trust.
只能向信赖的对象亮出底牌
You're so boring, Aki.
你还是一样死脑筋
It's okay.
没事啦 不要紧的
I want to ask your hobby.
我想问你们的兴趣
It says a lot about you as a person.
通过兴趣就能了解一个人
I'm Denji. I think I'm 16.
我叫淀治 年龄应该是16岁
My hobbies are eating and sleeping.
兴趣是吃东西跟睡觉
No way. That's so young.
天啊 这么年轻
You're not drinking, are you?
你应该没喝酒吧？
This is tea.
这是茶
I am Hirokazu Arai, 22 years old!
我叫做荒井博一 22岁
And I have a contract with the Fox Devil!
签约的恶魔是狐狸
My hobby is haiku!
兴趣是俳句
That's the same Devil Mr. Hayakawa is contracted with.
跟早前辈签约的恶魔一样耶
The Fox Devil is very friendly with humans.
狐狸恶魔对人类很友善
It has contracts with a lot of Devil Hunters.
跟不少恶魔猎人立下了契约
But only pretty people can use its head.
狐狸头部只有帅哥可以用喔
That Devil is very particular about looks.
因为那个恶魔很挑人外貌
I'm Kobeni Higashiyama. I'm 20…
我是东山小红 20岁
The Devil I have a contract with is… a secret.
签约的恶魔是…秘密
My hobby is eating tasty food.
兴趣是吃美食
Her dress is so cute.
穿得好可爱
It's from my big sister.
这是姐姐的旧衣服
-Eh? Where is your newbie, Fushi? -Kobeni has eight sisters. That's crazy.
-嗯？伏先生那边的新人呢？ -听说小红家是九个姐妹 不得了
Unfortunately, they died yesterday.
很遗憾
I'm shoo shorry!
南无阿弥陀佛
Resht… in… peesh…
法莲…法玄…夏经…
You're already drunk.
前辈已经醉了
They died so easily?
这么轻易就死了吗？
The Devils that civilian Hunters can't handle get passed to Public Safety.
毕竟民间处理不来的恶魔 会交给公安解决
People die faster than you can count.
会接二连三死不少人喔
None of those people started with me are here anymore.
和我同一届的也都不在公安了
Denji wants to kiss me, so he won't die.
淀治想跟我接吻 所以不会死
Himeno always kisses around when she's drunk.
姬野一喝醉就会跟人亲来亲去
Everyone except the newbies has been kissed by her.
除了在场的新人 大家都被她亲过
There's no escaping.
因为根本躲不掉
My kiss is guaranteed.
保证能接吻
I'll get my first kiss today.
今天我要献出初吻了
Kiss?
接吻？
Ms. Makima.
真纪真小姐
Excuse me. One beer, please.
不好意思 给我一杯生啤酒
Please sit here, Ms. Makima.
真纪真小姐 请坐这边
It's my first time seeing her in person.
我第一次看到真纪真小姐本人
Denji, are you going to kiss someone?
淀治 你要跟谁接吻吗？
I'm not!
我没有要亲
Denji, you don't want the kiss anymore?
淀治 你不想亲了吗？
I do!
我要亲
Excuse me. Another beer, please.
不好意思 再给我一杯生啤酒
So what's this kiss about?
然后呢 什么接吻？
I don't want Ms. Makima to see me kissing Ms. Himeno.
我不想让真纪真小姐 看见我跟姬野小姐接吻
It's off the table?
不亲吗？
But I want a French kiss just as bad.
但我想舌吻的心情也一样强烈
I need to change the subject for now.
现在只能先转移话题
Ms. Makima, guess what?
真纪真小姐 听我说
I found one of those Gun Devil things.
我捡到枪之恶魔的那个什么东西了
I heard. Well done, Denji.
我听说了 淀治你真厉害
Devils with Gun's pieces are appearing more frequently than ever.
从未这么快就出现持有肉片的恶魔
And that Devil that just targeted Denji.
包含上次攻击淀治的恶魔
There's something fishy about all this.
恶魔最近的动向不太对劲
Ms. Makima, do you know something about Denji?
真纪真小姐是不是知道淀治的底细？
Give me that!
那个也拿来
That's mine too!
那也是老子的
I'll tell you if you can outdrink me.
如果你酒量比我好 我就告诉你
Excuse me. Two beers, please.
不好意思 我要两杯生啤
I want to join. Another one for me.
我也要加入 再来一杯生啤
Horse meat. Fried chicken. Horse meat.
生马肉 炸鸡块 生马肉
Fried chicken!
炸鸡块
That's mine!
那盘也是老子的
Excuse me. Another one.
不好意思 再给我一杯生啤酒
By the way, you are impressive, Power.
话说回来 帕瓦真厉害
Very few Fiends can suppress their violent urges.
只有极少数魔人能抑制杀人的冲动
That's because I have a very high IQ!
因为老子智商很高
Is that determined by IQ?
这种事是取决于智商吗？
What is your IQ score?
你智商大概多少？
A hundred?
100吗？
Is that considered high? I think mine's around 100 as well.
100算高吗？我好像也是100左右
It's 120 then.
那就是120
That's specific. You must be very proud of it.
还特地记自己的智商 好像很得意似的
I think mine's 500… or 1,000…
老子好像有500吧…还是1000…
What's this?
天哪
She saw me! Ms. Makima saw me!
被看见了 被真纪真小姐看到了
This texture… Is it her tongue?
这个触感…是舌头吗？
It's so good. So soft.
好舒服 好软
It's so soft! What is this?
软软的 这是什么？
Her tongue? It's melting in my mouth.
是舌头吗？在嘴巴里融化了耶
Tongue… No!
舌头…
It's vomit!
是呕吐物
Now he's traumatized for life.
肯定会留下心理阴影
Excuse me. Could we have a rag or something?
不好意思 请给我抹布什么的
Oh, no. This is going to be bad.
糟了 这下完蛋了
Denji has a habit of swallowing anything nutritious in his mouth.
淀治有个习惯 会把嘴里有营养的东西吞下去
Pochita.
波奇塔 这个好像可以吃
Pochita, look over there.
波奇塔 快看那边
The rats are around some drunk's vomit.
老鼠都聚在醉汉的呕吐物那边
They're eating it! Can you believe it?
吃什么呕吐物 简直不敢相信
Such a shame for mammals.
同样是哺乳类 太丢脸了吧
Himeno does need more self-control.
姬野前辈那个人就是自制力不够
I'm good at helping sick people, right?
我很擅长催吐吧
That's because my mom got drunk after work all the time.
因为我经常照顾 下班后喝得烂醉的母亲
But I don't have your talent as a Devil Hunter.
我不像你一样 具有当恶魔猎人的天分
I really envy you.
真羡慕你
You envy me?
你说羡慕
Look at me.
看看我
My first kiss was with vomit.
初吻是呕吐物的味道
Why would you envy--
有什么好羡慕…
I'll take them to Hayakawa's house.
我会送早川一家回去
Ms. Makima paid for today.
这顿是真纪真小姐请客
Thank her, everyone.
大家要好好感谢她
Drinks paid by others are the best drinks you can get.
-用别人的钱喝酒最好喝了 -对啊
Himeno just carried him off.
姬野前辈刚才背着淀治离开了
So dark…
黑漆漆的…
Where am I?
这里是哪里？
Water…
水
Oh, that vomit lady.
对了 那个呕吐女
She kissed me with vomit.
给了我一个呕吐吻
Damn it.
可恶
Water…
水
Why are you at my place?
你怎么会跑来我家呢？
Did I bring you here?
是我带回来的吗？
I feel dizzy. What the hell?
头好晕 怎么搞的？
Oh right. You like Ms. Makima, don't you?
对了 你喜欢真纪真小姐吧？
My head's spinning.
头昏眼花
Jeez, Aki too.
讨厌 阿秋也是
Why does he have to act so shy?
还害羞成那样
Boo… Moo…
讨厌 哞…
Cow.
牛
Let's do it.
来做吧